photobook.com.my 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Photobook Malaysia

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to the Photobook Worldwide’s website (herein referred to as “Site”) provided by Photobook Worldwide (herein referred to as "Photobook Worldwide", “PBWW”, “we”, “us”, “our”, and their affiliates). By using our service, you fully accept and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy, which includes the privacy of your digital photographs and personal data and information you provide us.

**1\. Personal Information**

As we provide you our service of producing our range of Photobook Worldwide products, you may have to download our free [Photobook Designer](http://www.photobook.com.my/tools) where you will need to provide your name and valid email address. Where an order is made, we will also require relevant and compulsory billing and delivery information. Your personal information, including digital pictures that you voluntarily provide will be used only for the purpose for which you have provided them, and hence will not be shared or disclosed to any third parties **without your prior consent**. You may be asked to provide other optional information such as gender, contact numbers, camera makes, hobbies, and etc, where submitting such information is entirely voluntary. Access to this data is limited solely to authorized Photobook Worldwide staff only.

From time to time, we may use demographic data collected to tailor your experience on our website or use this information to send you contents, updates, new product offers and promotions that we feel might be relevant to you, based on the information that you furnished. We may sometimes also conduct surveys, promote sweepstakes and/or contests. You have the option to decline these mailings or choose to opt out at any time without sacrificing any rights in using or ordering any of services and products offered by Photobook Worldwide.

Photobook Worldwide reserves the right to disclose any relevant personal data under its sole discretion, with or without a warrant or court order from any and all global law enforcement agencies, if we believe that the disclosure is necessary to protect ourselves, or our business in certain situations such as, but not limited to, (a) are in violation of the Terms of Service governing this site; (b) have engaged, or are alleged to have engaged in any activity purporting to infringe upon the intellectual property rights of another; or (c) have engaged, or are alleged to have engaged in any other illegal conduct or activity. Photobook Worldwide also reserves the right to report any suspected illegal activity to such entities for investigation and prosecution.

**2\. Security**

Photobook Worldwide have engaged into a variety of industry-standard security technologies, procedures and processes and is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. When sensitive information (login data, credit card number, expiration date) is provided, encryption is performed using secure socket layer (SSL) technology. We do not store any credit card information. Though Photobook Worldwide undertakes the necessary steps to safeguard your Personal Information, note that Photobook Worldwide cannot fully eliminate all security risks, and is not liable for any losses that may results from unauthorized use of your credit card by any other third party.

**3\. Software License & Updates**

Photobook Designer is a royalty-free and non-exclusive Software provided by the Photobook Worldwide that allows customers to personally create and design professional photo books. Any updates, design and templates will also be considered as part of the Software. This Software is a non-transferable internal use license under the copyright to use, display, execute and perform for the sole purpose of creating photo books for production by Photobook Worldwide.

**4\. Book Content**

Upon uploading your book, you hereby acknowledge that the Content of the book conforms to the rules and regulations as stated in our [Terms of Service](http://www.photobook.com.my/return-policy/terms-of-use). Photobook Worldwide and all its subsidiaries reserve the right to refuse printing of any book that contains Content that breaches any of the agreements and privacy policies of the company. We will not print or publish any book or its contents unless authorization is given by the book's owner or author. It is your responsibility to alert Photobook Worldwide and all its subsidiaries if your book contains any explicit or sensitive content such as nudity and or profanity in order for special arrangements to be made when handling and producing your book. 

Once permission has been granted to Photobook Worldwide for usage of the book and its contents, Photobook Worldwide and all its subsidiaries reserve the right to use your photo book design, or any part thereof for marketing and promotional purposes, of which only books submitted successfully uploaded and ready to print using the Photobook Designer software will be accepted. We are not responsible for consumer-generated mistakes, such as but not limited to, spelling and spacing errors, alignment, lines and border issues, missing or incomplete files, or missing or incomplete images, once the file has been successfully uploaded into the system. We suggest customers to thoroughly check their proofs before uploading their books as we do not accept any amendments or changes once the file is uploaded.

**5\. Submission**

Note that content cannot be modified, changed or revised once your book design order has been uploaded onto the website. Photobook Worldwide has no obligation to review the Content that you have submitted and hence you hereby agree that your book has gone through the necessary proofs and checks until fully satisfied, and that it is ready to be published. You agree and understand that your book file is free from any computer viruses, worms or any software intended to harm, damage or alter a computer system or data before uploading it to our website. You further acknowledge that Photobook Worldwide is not required to keep electronic files of your book or maintain an archival copy of the printed book. Photobook Worldwide has no ownership in any of your book content.

**6\. Personal Information from Other Sources**

Photobook may attain Personal Information about you from other sources like telephone, fax or from other company websites. We may add this to our database we have already collected and collated to improve the products and services that we provide.

**7\. Marketing Provisions**

By creating an account with us, your email will be used as a communication tool for our products, services and updates. Emails may contain periodic newsletters, product updates, company announcements, promotional content, contests et cetera sent by our holding company, subsidiaries or local partners. We will not share, sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your e-mail address for commercial purposes without your consent. If you feel you have received an e-mail from us in error, please write to us at [support-ww@photobookworldwide.com](mailto:support-ww@photobookworldwide.com). At any time, if you no longer wish to receive a specific form of email, follow the "unsubscribe" instructions located near the bottom of each email. 

**8\. Copyright**

If you find that your book design has been copied or used in any Book in any manner that constitutes copyright infringement, please contact us immediately. Please view our Copyright for additional details and instructions. We will investigate and undertake the necessary measures upon obtaining all the required information for verification and authentication. In order to ensure the security of your information, Photobook Worldwide will periodically review this Privacy Policy and reserve the right at our sole discretion to update, revise or make modifications to the said policy from time to time. The date of this modification will be reflect at the top right of this page.

**9\. Contact Details and Location**

If you have a question regarding our Privacy Policy, or have questions that are not answered, please write to us at: Photobook Worldwide/Photobook Australia Attn: Legal, 1/475 Burwood Highway, Vermont South, Victoria 3133, Australia, or through our [Support](http://www.photobook.com.my/support) channels. Alternatively, you may reach us at +61 3 9887 6338 (AEST).
